<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 10:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Computing and Big Data Projects Based on AWS services</title>
      <link>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/ccbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/ccbd/</guid>
      <description>Sept 2022 - Dec 2022
1. Dining Concierge Assistant https://github.com/vvangmj/dining-concierge-assistant
TLDR Built a Dining Concierge chatbot that sends users restaurant suggestions given a set of preferences that you provide the chatbot with through conversation. 2. AI Photo Album https://github.com/vvangmj/ai-photo-album
TLDR Implemented a photo album web application that can be searched using natural language through both text and voice. You will learn how to use Lex, OpenSearch, and Rekognition to create an intelligent search layer to query your photos for people, objects, actions, landmarks and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demeter - All You Can Cook</title>
      <link>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/demeter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/demeter/</guid>
      <description>Sept 2022 - Dec 2022
Group Project for Software as a Service
Motivation Being a kitchen killer? Clogging mountains of food into your refrigerator while having no idea how to cook? Wanna show off your culinary skills when there’s a friend visiting?
Our Demeter App will assist you in all these scenes! Tapping the ingredients you have and clicking the “search” button, you’ll get all recipes for your target food materials, with calories calculated for your meal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsec - Recommend Interesting News for You in a Second</title>
      <link>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/newsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/newsec/</guid>
      <description>Sept 2022 - Dec 2022
Group Project for Cloud Computing and Big Data
Motivation Nowadays, people tend to access information from the internet with their mobile devices during small and fragmented moments. Due to the fast living pace, they are not patient enough to read over tedious news articles while trying to understand what’s happening with merely a news title may be too hard and presumptuous. Hence, we’re looking for an AWS service making it easier and more efficient for people to understand ideas of news through title, summary and important details retrieved from articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Database Projects</title>
      <link>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/advancedb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vvangmj.github.io/en/projects/advancedb/</guid>
      <description>Feb 2022 - May 2022
Group Projects for Advanced Database
1. Google Search Query Modification https://github.com/vvangmj/cs6111proj1
TLDR In order to learn a more accurate query intended by user, we use Rocchio algorithm to extract the relevant keyword that can support the accuracy of original search query.
2. Search Query Expansion Based on SpanBERT Algorithm https://github.com/vvangmj/cs6111proj2
TLDR In order to expand raw and obsure query into a more specific query, we implement the Iterative Set Expansion algorithm to extracts specified high quality relation informations from at most 10 webpages that returned by Google Custom Search Engine, and updates the query which will be used in the next search iteration according to the extraction results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
